<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on #whoami &lt;Eslam Salem&gt;</title>
    <link>http://eslam.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on #whoami &lt;Eslam Salem&gt;</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/286371?v=4</url>
      <link>https://avatars.githubusercontent.com/u/286371?v=4</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 09:47:06 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://eslam.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The unsecure node vm module</title>
      <link>http://eslam.io/posts/unsecure-node-vm/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Nov 2020 09:47:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eslam.io/posts/unsecure-node-vm/</guid>
      <description>As any nodejs developer you should often check the nodejs documentation look for new modules or new features or even a change in the current API. If you do you will notice a module called &amp;ldquo;VM&amp;rdquo; (Executing Javascript). This is a very interesting module as per nodejs documentation defination &amp;ldquo;The vm module enables compiling and running code within V8 Virtual Machine contexts&amp;rdquo;
Although the documentation state that &amp;ldquo;The vm module is not a security mechanism.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SSRF vulnerability in Uppy, Detected by Shieldfy</title>
      <link>http://eslam.io/posts/uppy-js-ssrf-vulnerability/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 09:47:06 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eslam.io/posts/uppy-js-ssrf-vulnerability/</guid>
      <description>In this post, we will explain how Shieldfy detected an SSRF ( Server-side request forgery ) vulnerability in Uppy, one of the popular packages in NPM, diving into the technical details of the vulnerability, exploitation and the fix.
Uppy is a sleek, modular JavaScript file uploader that integrates seamlessly with any application. It’s fast, easy to use and lets you worry about more important problems than building a file uploader. Uppy has more than 130,000 downloads a month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Practical Exploitation of Error Based Sql Injection</title>
      <link>http://eslam.io/posts/practical-exploitation-of-error-based-sql-injection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 15:43:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://eslam.io/posts/practical-exploitation-of-error-based-sql-injection/</guid>
      <description>Hi everybody I don’t post much write-ups online because most of the work done privately and under NDA.
But this time i decided to publish this (anonymously after website owner agreed ) because too many developers insists that you can’t exploit complicated SQL , or non result SQL (example: count(*) sql).
 Note: You can automate everything in this article using SQLMap, but i choose to exploit it manually to explain under the hood proccess.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
